This video gives a brief introduction to the Arclight's device.
Once attached, the sideshole of the direct ophthalmoscope will be placed directly over the
center of the lens that your mobile camera uses in the video mode.
The camera will function just like your eyes
when you are looking through the sideshole.
To confirm which lens to line up the
sidehole with, open the video app, or
your phone.
Place your finger over each lens in turn.
When the screen goes dark, you have covered
the lens used for video.
Remove the yellow paper from the back of the clip.
Place the points of the
arrow over the center of the lens used to capture video.
Press the clip down firmly.
Remove the arrow.
the clip should now be in the correct position.
To video the reflex switch on
the barectophthalboscope, end off the act lights and select the brightest light
with three clicks.
Make sure the lens rack is at the top.
With the light facing
away from the phone towards the patient, place the act lights in the clip and pull
pull the elastic over to secure.
Push the arc lights up until it cannot slide any further.
The slide hole of the direct of the oscilloscope will now be directly over
the center of the lens
that captures video.
To record the external eye, use the other end of the device.
To capture
image now, open the video app and zoom in filling the screen with the
view through the
site's home.
Press record and perform the examination.
Press stop and save the video.
You can now share with colleagues on secure encrypted platforms only for the purpose you
gain the concept from the patients.
Enjoy using the act lights in my job.